Guide to the Science fiction magazines, about 1946-2006.
Science fiction magazines
- Satellite Science Fiction, 1958 (Box 82)
- Saturn Science Fiction and Fantasy, 1958 (Box 82)
  Number of Issues: 1: 1
- Science Fiction Adventures, 1952 (Box 82)
- Science Fiction Adventures, 1953 (Box 83)
  Number of Issues: 4: Mar, Jul, Sep, Dec
- Science Fiction Adventures, 1954 (Box 83)
  Number of Issues: 2: Mar, May
- Science Fiction Digest, 1954 (Box 83)
  Number of Issues: 2: No. 1, 2
- Science Fiction Stories, 1955 (Box 83)
- Space Science Fiction, 1952 (Box 83)
- Star Science Fiction, 1958 (Box 83)
- Tales of the Frightened, 1957 (Box 83)
- Thrilling Science Fiction, 1971 (Box 83)
- Tops In Science Fiction, 1953 (Box 83)
- Unearth, 1977 (Box 83)
  Number of Issues: 4: Winter, Spring, Summer, Fall
  Notes: Summer: "Fragments of a Hologram Rose" by William Gibson
- Unearth, 1978 (Box 83)
  Number of Issues: 3: Winter, Spring, Summer
- Universe Science Fiction, 1954 (Box 83)
- Vanguard, 1958 (Box 83)
- Venture Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 83)
- Venture Science Fiction, 1957 (Box 84)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jul, Nov
- Venture Science Fiction, 1958 (Box 84)
  Number of Issues: 3: Jan, May, Jul
- Vortex Science Fiction, [1953] (Box 84)
- Weird Tales, 1953 (Box 84)
  Number of Issues: 2: Sept, Nov
- Weird Tales, 1954 (Box 84)
- Worlds Beyond, 1950 (Box 84)
- Worlds Beyond, 1951 (Box 84)
  Notes: 2 copies of Jan.
- Worlds of Fantasy, 1970-71 (Box 84)
- Worlds of Tomorrow, 1963 (Box 84)
  Number of Issues: 2: Jun, Aug
- Worlds of Tomorrow, 1964 (Box 84)
- Analog, 1963 (Box 85)
  Notes: Continues from digest size; 2 copies of Mar. and Oct.; Dec.-(Feb. 1964): Dune World [Dune] by Frank Herbert
- Analog, 1964 (Box 86)
- Analog, 1965 (Box 87)
  Notes: Jan.-(May): Prophet of Dune [Dune Messiah] by Frank Herbert; returns to digest size Apr. 1965
- Cosmos Science Fiction and Fantasy, 1977 (Box 87)
- Fantasy: Review of Fantasy and Science Fiction, 1984 (Box 87)
- Fantasy Book, [1947] (Box 87)
- Galileo, [1976] (Box 87)
- Galileo, [1977] (Box 87)
  Number of Issues: 3: No. 3-5
- Galileo, [1978] (Box 88)
  Number of Issues: 4: No. 6-8, 10
- Galileo, [1979] (Box 88)
  Number of Issues: 3: No. 11/12, 13, 15
  Notes: 11/12 double issue
- Satellite, 1959 (Box 88)
- Science Fiction Age, 1992 (Box 88)
  Number of Issues: 1: Nov.
- Science Fiction Plus, 1953 (Box 88)
  Number of Issues: 2: Mar, Apr
  Notes: 3 copies of Mar and Apr
- Tomorrow Speculative Fiction, 1993 (Box 88)